- [JUNE] Hey!
- [PING GRUNTS]
- Ow!
What's with you, huh?!
Why do you have a copy of
our birth certificates?
I wanted to check if you're
really related to Don Nato.
Why are you dragging Ima
into all of this?
If you have a problem
with me,
- leave her out of it.
- Okay.
Fine. Listen.
I checked your social
media accounts
and there's no record of
you being in a relationship.
You said it yourself, right?
Why are you acting
like this now?
You seem eager
to get married.
Are you that
desperate for money?
Just so you know,
everyone is desperate
for money.
Why should I be ashamed
of my dream
to give Ima and my family
a better life?
I'm willing to do anything.
We don't stop working...
but it's still hard for us
to make both ends meet.
We're not rich
like you.
You don't understand how
hard it is to be poor.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You think I came
from money?
Well, listen.
My father...
was Don Nato's driver.
He treated us like family...
and he helped us grow
our business.
Everything I have now...
I owe it all to him.
So I'm sorry if you're upset
at what I'm doing.
But I will protect everything
Don Nato worked hard for.
Well, sorry.
I thought you were
born rich.
That's the problem
with you.
You think you know me.
Wow! That's rich
coming from you.
You already judged me
the first time we met.
If you think about it,
we're both doing this
for our families.
I'm doing this for Ima, and
you're doing this for Don Nato.
Right?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey!
Hey! Why do you always pick
fights with me?
OMG!
Our first lovers' quarrel!
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, it'd be good if I
could put you on mute.
I wish you were
just a standee.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
You find me pretty,
don't you?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
What a snob.
Plan B.
Shower Papa Ping with lots
of affection.